少数族裔犯事作乱
minorities are criminals,
性爱很恶心  却很有趣
sex is sick, but interesting.
问问自己  "什么东西会吓着奶奶
Ask yourself, "What would scare my grandmother,
或气死爷爷"
"Or piss off my grandfather?"
那就是福克斯的新闻  你在记吗
And that's a Fox story. Are you writing this down?
这样就说得通了
It makes so much sense.
-恐吓  激怒  -好的
- Frighten, titillate. - Right.
恐吓  激怒  恐吓  激怒
Frighten, titillate. Frighten, titillate.
报道的开始  得需要一个明确的反派
When you're starting the story, you need to start with a clear villain.
自由派法官  没头脑市长
Liberal judge, pinhead mayor,
佛蒙特  好莱坞
Vermont, Hollywood.
保守派想恪守保守主义
Conservatives want to conserve.
宝贝  你是抵御
You're the last defense
恨耶稣  爱变性
against Jesus-hating, trans-loving,